Dipali Makad<u>ia</u>

Graduate Student

☑ dipali.makadia@gmail.com 📞 +1 (562) 825-8686 👂 Los Angeles, CA

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/dipali-makadia/

Summary

Creative and Enthusiastic grad student pursuing Masters of Science in Computer Science, seeking to gain new experience to expand my knowledge and skills and apply it to every challenging problem to give a great performance in every opportunity and also I have more than 3 years of work experience in Front end development. Extensive experience in HTML5, CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap, Highcharts, Handlebar, Grunt/Gulp, JavaScript, ¡Query, JSON, Ajax, W3C Standards ,NPM, React, Responsive Web Development. Have some knowledge and worked very little in WordPress, Google Cloud, Google tag manager, Adobe Targets, AWS, firebase, and Photoshop. Hands-on experience in implementing website structure and navigation layout on various platforms and devices. Always ready to explore new platforms and work on them. Good experience working in a team and providing a quality product to the client.

Professional Experience

03/2022 - present Los Angeles, US

Graduate Student Assistant at Office of Graduate Studies

California State University, Los Angeles

I am working as a Thesis Reviewer at the Office of Graduate Studies at California State University, Angeles.

My work is to review the thesis of the students. Mainly I check the format of the thesis which is in Microsoft word and pdf and email them the correction which they need to do. Meet students over zoom and review their thesis.

06/2022 - 08/2022 Los Angeles, US

Student Assistant at Office of Graduate Studies

California State University, Los Angeles

I worked as a Student Assistant with the Office of Graduate Studies for the summer. As a student assistant, various tasks are assigned to me like answering phone calls, and emails and also making flyers, spreadsheets, etc.

05/2021 - 01/2022 Pune, India

Programmer Analyst

Cognizant □

O2 - O2 is a cognizant client and the project involves the development of the front end using HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, GIT, and Adobe Target.

05/2019 - 05/2021 Mumbai, India

Associate Interface Developer

Digitas India 🛮

DMI Project - The project involves the development of graphs and frontend using HTML5, CSS3, Jquery, Highcharts, GIT, and Handlebars.

My Role:

- Developed 4 pages of different charts using Highcharts and other pages using frontend technologies like HTML, SCSS, and Jquery.

06/2018 - 02/2019 Mumbai, India

Software Engineer

Motes & Bots Technologies

Smart Office -- The project involves a dashboard for Office. In which admin can log in and allow to register only those who have rights. It contains various modules like Add Employee, Manage Group, Manage Logs, and Access Rights. It also includes CRUD operations of employees. Technologies Used -ReactJs, Firebase, NodeJS, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap.

My Role:

- Developing Dashboard using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and ReactJS.
- Making Database Tables on Firebase.
- Different Components and Routing in ReactJS.

07/2017 - 06/2018 Bangalore, India

Intern

Textron □

Request Tracker -- The project involves tracking requests so that the current status of a particular request will be known. Technologies used - C#, HTML, CSS, SQL Server. This is my final year MTECH project & I had been part of this project during my internship. My Role:

- Developing a dashboard using HTML, and CSS.
- Creating Database Tables
- Testing

Education

01/2022 - present Los Angeles,

Masters Of Science, Computer Science California State University, Los Angeles ☑

United States of America

GPA - 3.9/4

Email id - dmakadi@calstatela.edu

08/2016 - 07/2018 India

Masters Of Technology, Computer Science & Information Security Manipal Institute of Technology ☑

GPA - 7.03/10

08/2012 - 07/2016

India

Bachelor Of Engineering, Information Technology

Gujarat Technological University □

GPA - 7.18/10

Skills

HTML **CSS**

SCSS

Bootstrap

Javascript

Jquery

ReactJS

VueJS

AngularJS

NPM

GIT

Highcharts

Bower

Handlebars

JSON

MongoDB

NodeJS

Java

Python

Nodemailer

† Technologies

Wordpress Google Tag Manager

Adobe Targets

Google Cloud

AWS

Firebase

Photoshop **Eclipse**

Visual Studio Code Jupyter Notebook

Postman